Jeremy Dayniel David

Web Developer

With over 5 years of experience in web development, I excel at creating innovative, user-friendly websites. My diverse project experience, ranging from simple sites to complex systems, has equipped me with a comprehensive skill set.

Work Experience

Frontend Web Developer, Sunnybyte (Remote, CA, USA)

Sept 2022 - Sept 2023

- Worked with clients like Toyota, U.S. POLO ASSN., and LabCentral.
- Develop thoughtful, frontend solutions to client needs and implement them with best practices for code quality, structure, commenting and extensibility in mind.
- Building and modifying web pages with strong development and design principles ensuring the code is always better than it was before.
- Maintaining projects and updates all required packages and plugins every quarter.
- Collaborate with project managers and other developers for estimation, planning, and development.

Web Developer, NIXIQ (Dubai, UAE)

Jul 2020 - Oct 2021

- Develop and maintain in-house and client projects.
- Worked with interesting projects like cryptocurrency exchange market and cryptocurrency wallet specifically Aidos Kuneen.
- Mentor other developer through close collaboration sharing my knowledge and experience.
- Handle deployments and web hosting to other projects.

Fullstack Developer, iTreat (Dubai, UAE)

Feb 2020 - Jun 2020

 Worked together with developers for developing website, web application, and mobile application.

Web Developer, Fullstack HQ (Angeles City, Philippines)

May 2019 - Mar 2019

 Converting design into pixel perfect HTML website, Wordpress, or Shopify.

- Philippines
- https://jeremydavid.is-a.dev
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/
 jeremydaynieldavid/
- jddavid@protonmail.com
- +639626932565

Skills

Programming Languages

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, PHP, Node.js, SQL, NoSQL

Templating Languages

Twig, Nunjucks, Liquid

Libraries & Frameworks

React, Next.js, Vue, Express, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, Eleventy

Content Management Systems

Wordpress, Craft CMS, Shopify, Headless CMS

Tools & Platforms

Git, Github, Gitlab, Vercel, Netlify, DigitalOcean, AWS, Figma, Adobe PS, Adobe XD

Education

Holy Angel University

Bachelor of Science Major in Computer Science, 2018